Wish you a happy new year, sir!
Wish you the same...
You can drink the rest, Nobi-san.
Yamaguchi-san, you have some too...
Why, thank you...
Mister, HAPPY NEW YEAR!
Don't interrupt us!
Why are you so upset?
That guest drank tons of beer...
but even forgot to bring me a new year's souvenir.
New year's present is a most awaited thing for kids like me.
But how dare he forgot...!
I see. In that case...
New year's present!
Are you trying to mock me?
You can get real presents if you pull this ball.
You mean it?
Well, wait and watch how
I'd forgot to give you this.
Oh yes, Thanks!
It's unfair that only you received the present.
Alright, I'll get one too...
Sorry, I'd forgot. Nobi-kun, was it your name?
Thanks so much.
I wish more guests arrive to our house one after another.
Uncle Muneshi?
He's my father's little brother...
He is obsessed with treasure hunting.
He only comes to drink and eat tons during the new year...
But he's #1 cheapskate who won't even bring a present to me.
I see. So you want new year's present all the more so badly.
Alright, this time I'm getting my new year's present.
Heave ho!
Ah, it's not working!